// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [


{
    numb:1,
    question:"What type of CSS is the following code snippet <h1 style='color: blue;'> A Blue Haeding </h1>",
    answer:"A. Inline",
    options:[
    "A. Inline",
    "B. Internal",
    "C. EXternal",
    "D. None of the above",
    ]
},

{
    numb:2,
    question:"In the below code snipped, in what order will thw amrgin be added ? p{ margin: 25px 50px 75px 100px; }",
    answer:"A. Top,Right,Bottom,Left",
    options:[
    "A. Top,Right,Bottom,left",
    "B. Top,Left,Bottom,Right",
    "C. Top,Bottom,Right,Left",
    "D. Right,Left,Top,Bottom",
    ]
},

{
    numb:3,
    question:"What will be the width of the div element gaie=ven below? div{ margin:310px; padding:20px; border:5px solid blue;margin:0px}",
    answer:"C. 360px",
    options:[
    "A. 310px",
    "B. 350px",
    "C. 360px",
    "D, None of the above",
    ]
},

{
    numb:4,
    question:"Which of the following CSS properties specifies the stack order os elements?",
    answer:"A. z-index",
    options:[
    "A. z-index",
    "B. overlap",
    "C. No such specific property is present",
    "D. None iof the above",
    ]
},

{
    numb:5,
    question:"What value should be passed to thw width parameter if we what an element,say a table, to span the entire width of the screen?",
    answer:"A. 100%", 
    options:[
    "A. 100%",
    "B. 50%",
    "C. 0%",
    "D.NOone of the above",
    ]
},

{
    numb:6,
    question:"What are the uses of CSS pseudo-elements?",
    answer:"D. All the above",
    options:[
    "A. Style specified parts of an element",
    "B. Style the first letter or line of an element",
    "C. Insert content before or after the element",
    "D. All the above",
    ]
},

{
    numb:7,
    question:"What are the dofferent types of gradients in CSS?",
    answer:"D. All the above",
    options:[
    "A. Liner Gradients",
    "B. Conic Gradients",
    "C. Radial Gradients",
    "D. All the above",
    ]
},

{ 
    numb:8,
    question:"The transparent keyword is equivalent to which RGBA() value in CSS?",
    answer:"C. RGBA(0,0,0,0)",
    options:[
    "A. RGBA(0,0,0,1)",
    "B. RGBA(255,255,255,1)",
    "C. RGBA(0,0,0,0)",
    "D. RGBA(255,255,255,0)",
    ]
},

{
    numb:9,
    question:"what is the general syntax of writing the var() function?",
    answer:"A. var(--name,value)",
    options:[
    "A. var(--name.vakue)",
    "B. var(--name)",
    "C. var(value)",
    "D. None of the above",
    ]
},

{
    numb:10,
    question:"True or False:In the CSS box model,the content area of an element includes padding and borders?",
    answer:"B. False",
    options:[
    "A. True",
    "B. False",
    ]
}
   


  
];